Thank you.
The board is regular meeting of the Miami-Specially
Intelli-A-40.
For today's day at 5.30-7pm out of tune as
Invocation by the Dean of all Saints at Piscone Church.
Ms. Cabe, I'm a Hake, thanks for being here.
Thank you.
Let us pray.
Well, while you got ahead of me, father,
said that the air in Pile Bios can pull off this in this city.
The spirit of wisdom, charity, and justice.
That with steadfast purpose, they may
faithfully serve in their offices
to promote the well-being of all people.
Through Jesus Christ, I'm Lord.
Amen.
Roger that.
I pledge allegiance to the Father of the United States of America,
and to the Republic for which it stands.
One nation under God, in this world, with liberty and justice for all.
Thank you.
I don't feel as public to put on schedule personal parents
as anyone in the arts.
It was just to address the authority on any agenda item.
They're being known item five as a consent agenda.
Staff is recommending items six to 10 of the consent agenda.
Most of them are.
Okay.
We have a second.
Say.
Go, Paul, please.
Johnson.
All right.
Let's go.
I'm 11.
There's new business.
Any new business?
You had some new business goes up to the next meeting.
Right.
Any other new business?
So being nine staff are fortunate in your packet.
Any questions for staff?
No.
I'm a medical man.
Okay.
Item 13 is trustee community announcements.
Any announcements?
Anyone?
Item 14 is adjourned.
So we have the motion to adjourn.